// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " To create HTML page, you need?",
    answer: "Both [A] and [B]",
    options: [
      "Web browser",
      "text editor",
      "Both [A] and [B]",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "a are the tags used for?",
    answer: "Adding links to your page",
    options: [
        "Adding image",
        "Aligning text",
        "Audio-voiced text",
        "Adding links to your page",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The BODY tag is usually used after?",
    answer: "HEAD tag",
    options: [
      "HTML tag",
      "EM tag",
      "TITLE tag",
      "HEAD tag"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What does the br tag add to your webpage?",
    answer: " Line break",
    options: [
      "Long break",
      "Paragraph break",
      " Line break",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What does XML stand for?",
    answer: "eXtensible Markup Language",
    options: [
      "eXtensible Markup Language",
      "eXecutable Multiple Language",
      "eXTra Multi-Program Language",
      "eXamine Multiple Language"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which type of language is Javascript ?",
    answer: " Line break",
    options: [
      " Programming",
       "Scripting",
    "Markup",
    "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which is not valid data type in Javascript ?",
    answer: "  float",
    options: [
      "Undefinded",
      "Boolean",
      "float",
      "Number",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Gif and jpg are the two main types of what?",
    answer: "images",
    options: [
      "videos",
      "Paragraph break",
      " animated effects",
      "images"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Increasing the cellpadding means ?",
    answer: "Increase the distance between cell and content",
    options: [
      "Increase the softness of your site",
      "Increase the space between cells",
      "Increase the distance between cell and content",
      "All of the above",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Adding a border to your image helps the visitor to recognize it as what?",
    answer: " A link",
    options: [
      "A frame",
      "A link" ,
      "A picture",
      " None of the above",
    ]
  },
];